[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What hired assassin is assigned to kill James Bond, in From Russia With Love?", "correct_answer": "Donald (Red) Grant", "incorrect_answers": ["Max Zorin", "Emile Locque", "Peter Franks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia means abnormal fear of what?", "correct_answer": "Long words", "incorrect_answers": ["River animals", "Large animals", "Pachyderms"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was the movie Lean on Me based on a true story?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of an alcoholic beverage consisting of equal parts of lager beer and lemonade?", "correct_answer": "radler", "incorrect_answers": ["mazout", "spavola", "russ"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many Emmy Awards did reporter John Donvan win in the 1990s?", "correct_answer": "2", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "he is not a reporter", "none"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "WETYIAFHKLXVNM\nQRUOPSDGJCB\nIn which of these rows would the letter Z  go?", "correct_answer": "top", "incorrect_answers": ["bottom", "neither", "none"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This sequel earned more at the box office than the original film. Its song Glory of Love was a #1 hit in the US and was nominated for an Oscar.", "correct_answer": "Karate Kid II", "incorrect_answers": ["Eye of the Tiger", "Beverly Hills Cop II", "Star Trek IV: The Voyage Home"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What magazine does James Bond take away from Bern lawyer Gumbolds office in On Her Majestys Secret Service?", "correct_answer": "Playboy", "incorrect_answers": ["Time", "Der Spiegel", "Life"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ploughmans Lunch is traditional for this country. It consists of cheese, a bit of pickle and pickled onion, and a slice of bread.", "correct_answer": "England", "incorrect_answers": ["Wales", "Scotland", "Ireland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The west half of the island of New Guinea is part of Indonesia, which comprises how many islands?", "correct_answer": "17,508", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "8,407", "247,542"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor was considered for the role of Willy Wonka in the 2005 movie Charlie and the Chocolate Factory, before it was given to Johnny Depp?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Brad Pitt", "Jim Carrey", "Nicolas Cage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is usually a disadvantage in chess?", "correct_answer": "An isolated pawn", "incorrect_answers": ["A castled king in the opening", "A passed pawn", "A centralized king in the ending"]}]